You are homeless.
That is, there is no house.
Yes, Man of God.
You paid money somewhere and
they refused to give you receipt.
Yes, Man of God.
Okay, don't worry. What happened to your former house?
It was burned by neighbours.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Josephine Iweke.
I am from Imo State, residing in Abuja.
I am a teacher, teaching at a junior
secondary school.
I was in the first service when the man
of God came to me and said,
"Sister, you are homeless. What
happened to your former house?"
I got up and said, "It's true, Man of
God. It was burnt by neighbours".
After they burned it, the people that I am working with in the educational department
said that my life was not safe in that village.
So they transferred me to a town where I began to work in the school there.
The cost of living inside town was very difficult for me, with what I was passing through.
I asked my principal if she could get me a place to sleep at.
She said she did not have but asked if I could manage to sleep in the classroom after school.
I told her that I could manage.
After school, I would bring out my things where I had hidden them,
sweep the floor and sleep on a mat somebody had given me.
I would sleep on a mat next to the security man.
First thing in the morning, I would fetch water from the borehole, bathe and dress up.
Other teachers thought that I used to come to school very early.
I used to be punctual.
They were seeing me but didn't even know what had happened.
My principal was shedding tears. She said that she didn't want anybody to know
that I was staying there as a female teacher, for my safety.
That is how I became homeless in Abuja, up till now.
When we closed for this vacation, I went home to see my parents.
My mother then started crying because the case was in court.
The commissioner of police took the case to court against the person they had caught.
Then I came here with my parents.
The man of God prophesied to me that I was homeless. Up till now, I am homeless.
Everything in my bedroom got burnt. I had two rooms.
The other room had a plastic chair and a small television.
So, everything I had was burnt down.
When we resumed, I would go home and continue sleeping in the school.
Just tell us, for how long have you been in this condition?
Since January 30th when this thing happened, I have been sleeping in the classroom
because immediately the Education Department that I am working with
transferred me and intervened with the help of human rights activists
to whom the case was reported to.
I have been homeless. People have been assisting me.
We have heard from Mrs Josephine Iweke explain
how her house and possessions were burnt and as a result of this,
she had no other option but to sleep on the floor of the school in which she teaches.
Prophet T. B. Joshua gives Mrs Josephine Iweke a cash sum of 1 million naira to rebuild herself.
In addition to the 1 million naira, she is also presented with three bags of rice.
Thank You, Lord. Thank You, my God.
The Lord of Synagogue, the Lord of Prophet T. B. Joshua,
the Lord that created all of us, thank You!
Actually, teachers are the step that brought everybody to where you are.
Thank You, Lord, for seeing me through.
We have many good samaritans in our midst who feel what others are feeling
We have listened to the plight of this woman.
In addition to this cash gift of 1 million naira from the anointed man of God and three bag of rice,
we want to call on the good samaritans in our midst
as the Spirit of God has touched your heart, to also make a contribution to this woman.
Please, can you step forward and also give your contribution to this woman.
She deserves our help.
Deeply touched by what Prophet T. B. Joshua had done for this woman,
many people from the congregation came out to help in their own way.
Remember, a time to give is not a time to show off but a time to reshape our destiny.
I am adding the sum of N100,000 to
what the man of God has given her.
My name is Bodis from Bayelsa State.
On behalf of my wife, my son and my daughter, I am giving her N500,000.
Shall we clap for Jesus Christ!
My name is Mr Emmanuel Nmankwo from Abuja, Nigeria.
I am supporting the man of God with N100,000.
Thank you very much.
My name is Mr Pascal Odiegwu.
On behalf of my family, I am supporting the man of God with N200,000.
When we give, we create for ourselves a purse that does not grow old.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Josephine Iweke.
I am from Imo State, residing in Abuja.
I am very happy and grateful for what
God has used Prophet T. B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV partners all
over the world to do in my life.
Honestly, they have reformed my
life, they have changed my life
to another level because I
was homeless before.
I had nowhere to sleep, nowhere to lay my head.
I came to The SCOAN hoping to be prayed for and be delivered, out of this problem.
On Sunday, the first week of September, I was here.
The man of God came to me and prophesied that I was homeless.
He asked me what had happened to my former house.
I was shocked because the prophecy was very correct.
100% correct.
You are homeless.
That is, there is no house.
Yes, Man of God.
And you paid money somewhere and they refused to give you a receipt.
Okay, don't worry. What happened to your former house?
It was burned by neighbours.
It was as if he had entered my mind to because that was what brought me here.
I was homeless because they burnt my house.
I had been roaming about with nowhere to stay, sleeping in a classroom
where I was reposted as a teacher.
The prophecy is very correct.
I was afraid but the day that I received the prophecy,
I was relieved that my problem was solved.
I was happy, jumping that my problem had been solved.
To my greatest surprise, the man of God gave me the sum of 1 million naira, three bags of rice
and a copy of 'The Mirror'.
I was shocked because I never expected this.
I was glorifying God for my prophecy, that my problem was solved.
I didn't know he would follow it up to this extent.
The follow-up was a surprise to me.
I was shocked and happy.
I didn't expect that.
My mind is like that of a new-born baby.
After that, he also told the
Emmanuel TV Partners to assist.
and a lot of them came out and contributed.
The man of God also presented it
to me - an additional two million naira,
apart from the one million naira he had given me.
I am now the owner of 3,000,000 naira from my daddy,
Prophet T. B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners.
I am so happy; the follow-up he did is too much for me.
I never expected this.
I want to use this opportunity to thank Prophet T. B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners
for all their hospitality and kind gestures towards me.
They have changed my life not only materially but also spiritually,
because since being here, I have been receiving prayer, attending Bible class.
and praying all the time. I am now really
born again.
I am now closer to God and I will
never go back again in my life.
Nothing will make me go back again because I have seen that
a person who is in the Lord has everything
and in the Lord, everything will come, even in a way you did not expect.
More blessings are coming from God.
God is my beginning and end.
I have given my life wholeheartedly to God from today henceforth.
Thank You, Lord.
We are advising you to live your
life to please God.
You are healed, delivered and
blessed to stay and follow Christ.
God Almighty will strengthen you to follow Him in truth and in His way in Jesus Christ's name.
Amen. I am a child of God.
Thank You, Jesus, for blessing me,
for using Prophet T. B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV Partners for
blessing me spiritually and materially.
Thank You, Jesus!
My advice to the world is that you should hold on to God anyhwere you are
and in every situation because you with God are majority.
Don't give up because you say that you don't have anybody.
You with God are majority.
As Christians, remember that in the
world that cares less, we should care more
because whatever you give to the relief of the poor
and for God's support, that you give unto God.
This is a remarkable day in the life of Mrs Josephine Iweke
as she says, Thank You, Jesus, for everything.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.